

## **DATA DIRI**

## **Date and Place of Birth**

Jakarta, March 31st 2008

#### Gender

Male

#### **Status**

Single

# **Nationality**

Indonesia

## **CONTACT**

- +62 82111557981
- michaelsatrian@gmail.com
- Jl. BBD III Blok B1 no. 105, Mekarsari, Cimanggis, Depok, 16452

# **SOCIAL MEDIA**

@m\_satria31

https://mic3103.github.io/port ofolio-michael/

# **ABOUT ME**

A web developer with 2 years of experience specializing in frontend development. My 6 years of experience in video editing allows me to bring a unique perspective and contribute effectively to web development projects that demand a strong visual understanding.

## **EDUCATION**

SMA MARSUDIRINI BOGOR 2023-NOW

SMP MARSUDIRINI BOGOR 2020-2023

SD PERMATA BUNDA CIMANGGIS 2014-2020

### **EXPERIENCES**

#### **OSIS SMP MARSUDIRINI BOGOR**

Multimedia Division (2021-2022)

#### **OSIS SMA MARSUDIRINI BOGOR**

ICT Development Division (2023-2024)

#### **Coding & Web Design**

 Achieved 2nd Place in the Web Design Competition at KBOF 2024

#### Video Editing

- Achieved 2nd Place in the Short Movie Competition at M-Fest:UROZION 2019
- Video Editor & Multimedia at Marsudirini Bogor Dormitory

# **SKILLS**

- Proficient in programming languages HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, PHP, and JavaScript.
- Skilled in Video Editing & Visual Effects using Filmora and Adobe After Effects.